(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
真時代に響いてよ my howling
Echo through the new era, my howling
Howling
作詞・作曲 ZAQ
Lyrics & Composition: ZAQ
とうとうと流れてく風景
The scenery flowing along endlessly
刹那的な日々の中で
In the midst of these fleeting days
差し伸べられた手は優しく
The hand reached out was gentle
鼓動に滴る
Dripping into my heartbeat...
微熱を予感
...a premonition of a slight fever
風に逆らう そう生きてきたから
Against the wind, that's how I've lived
君に会って気づく もう一人じゃない
Meeting you, I realize I'm not alone anymore
叫ぼう 瞬きは声を
Let's shout, our voices flickering
月へ響く
Echoing to the moon
爪弾く未知 孤高の群れ
A path of plucking, a solitary pack
共に咆哮をあげる
Raising a roar together
濃く伝播する想いは
The thoughts that propagate deeply
心強くする
Make the heart stronger
付いておいでよ 後ろに君がいるから
Follow me, because you're behind me
私は迷わない 光射す道へ
I won't hesitate, towards the path where the light shines
無力だから仲間を求め
Seeking comrades because I'm powerless
凍えるから火を灯して
Lighting a fire because I'm freezing
変化と共に進化してゆく
Evolving along with the changes
この結末は誰も知らない
Nobody knows how this will end
…君を信じる
...I believe in you.
そう決めているから
Because that's what I've decided.
どんな異常事態も
No matter how abnormal the situation,
乗り越えられるよ
I can overcome it.
月光、この闇に唯一
Moonlight, the only one in this darkness,
凛と咲く花
a flower blooming with dignity.
恐れなのか 憧れなのか
Is it fear? Or is it longing?
深め合う夜空
The night sky deepening together.
大地を駆けるゲル
A girl racing across the earth,
私と君が紡ぎ出す
the story that you and I
物語
weave together.
単純な未来じゃない
It's not a simple future.
湧き立つ情熱
Surging passion,
この声に乗せよう
let's put it on this voice.
空飛ぶ羽根なくても
Even if we don't have wings to fly,
手はつなげられたから
we could still hold hands.
この運命を選んだ
I chose this fate.
連動する遠吠えは
The linked howls
四島に響いて
echo across the four islands.
何度も何度も
Again and again,
その絆を
those bonds,
確かめ合った
we confirmed with each other.
待ってた記憶が
The memories I've been waiting for
鮮明に響く
echo vividly.
つま弾く道 孤高の群れ
The path played, the solitary pack,
ともに嘆く夜
the night we grieve together.
慟哭 電波で
Lamentation, through the airwaves,
想いはここで
feelings grow
強くなる
stronger here.
共に行こう
Let's go together,
隣に君がいるから
because you are by my side.
私は迷わない
I won't hesitate,
光射す道へ
towards the path where the light shines.
Listen to my Howling
狼は止まることはない
The wolf never stops.
はい、というわけで1曲目は
Alright, so that first song was
「Howling」でしたー！
"Howling"!
みんな、大神ミオ4周年記念ライブ
Everyone, thank you for coming to Ookami Mio's
「Mio Forest night party」に
4th Anniversary Live, "Mio Forest Night Party"!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for joining me!
嬉しいよ！
I'm so happy!
えっとですね、今回こちらのね
Um, so about this
タグなんですけれども
hashtag here...
「#大神ミオ4周年記念」
"#OokamiMio4thAnniversary."
ということで
Since that's what it is,
ぜひこちらのタグで
I'd be really happy if you
呟いてくれるとすごい嬉しいです
could tweet with this tag.
スクショもいっぱい撮ってね！
Take lots of screenshots too!
というわけでね、あの今回ね
So, about the live
ライブステージなんかいい感じに
stage this time... I thought it had
星いっぱい付いてるなと思ったんですけど
a nice touch with all these stars, but...
こちらのステージと
For this stage,
あとこちらのロゴですね
and also this logo here...
こちらを、いつもお世話になっております
I asked Sakusai-sei, who I'm
サクサイセイ様にお願いいたしました
always indebted to, to create them.
デザインありがとうございます！
Thank you for the design!
あ、ちょっと引きで撮ってくれてる
Oh, they're taking a wide shot.
すごい可愛いんだよ、このデザインが
This design is so cute.
いっぱい星流れてるしね
There are lots of shooting stars too.
というわけでね、えー、まあ
Anyway, well, after receiving
いっぱいお祝いしてもらいまして
so many congratulations...
まだまだ始まったうちのライブなんですけれども
My live concert has just begun,
始まったばかりのね
it's only the beginning.
ゲストの方も来てもらっているらしい！
I heard some guests are coming too!
誰なんだ一体！？ということで
I wonder who they are!? Anyway,
最後まで楽しんでってね、みんな！
please enjoy until the end, everyone!
あ、なんか次の曲の準備しなきゃいけないみたい
Oh, looks like I need to get ready for the next song.
じゃ、ちょっと行ってくるね！
Well, I'll be off for a bit!
行ってきまーす！
I'm going!
画面越し　今日も見えている
Even today, I see it through the screen.
いつもと変わりない笑顔
That same smile you always wear...
纏うそれは仮面か
is it a mask?
本当の自分を教えて
Tell me your true self.
着飾り澄まし顔じゃなく
Not the dressed-up, composed face,
呆れるほど臆病な
but the one that's shockingly cowardly.
It's all or nothing
真実を Open my heart
Open my heart to the truth.
君に全てを
I want you to
受け止めて欲しい
accept everything.
加速していく
Living in a world
世界で生きてく僕ら
that keeps accelerating,
聞き飽きたよ
we're tired of hearing
比べたがりの声
voices that love to compare.
位置付けられた
If it's a
運命ならば
predetermined fate,
抗うよ
I'll resist it.
見つけるよ
I'll find it.
僕である理由
The reason why I am me.
可愛いだけじゃ
We can't just
もういられない
be cute anymore.
声を上げていくんだ
We're going to raise our voices:
STARDUST SONG
精一杯 足元見るだけで精一杯
Doing my best, just looking at my feet is all I can do
何をしてるような僕には
For someone like me, who seems to be doing nothing
君に触れることはできるのかな
I wonder if I can ever reach you
Please me, answer 簡単だ
Please me, answer, it's simple
Feeling myself 君と
Feeling myself, with you
呼応する 心のまま
Resonating, just as my heart desires
飛び出せ！
Take flight!
加速していく 世界で生きていく僕ら
Accelerating, we live in this world
未知の方へ 歩むことはやめない
We won't stop walking towards the unknown
一か八かの 駆け出しだとしても構わない
I don't care if it's a make-or-break start
立ち向かうよ 頂を目指すそのために
I'll face it, to aim for the summit
最高潮の執着 それは全力の中に
The ultimate obsession lies within giving it your all
声は力に変わる
Voices turn into power
あと少し もう迷うことはない
Just a little more, I won't hesitate anymore
僕だけの道しるべ 胸に刻んで
Carving my own signpost into my heart
加速していく 世界で生きていく僕ら
Accelerating, we live in this world
聞き飽きたよ 比べたがりの声
I'm tired of hearing voices that love to compare
一かゼロか 決められた運命ならば
If it's a predetermined fate of one or zero
抗うよ 見つけるよ 僕である理由
I'll resist, I'll find the reason for being me
いつでも僕ら シンクロしていたい
We want to be in sync always
今を輝くんだ Stardust
Shine in the now, Stardust
可愛いだけじゃ もういられない
I can't just be 'cute' anymore
声を上げていくんだ Stardust
Raise your voice, Stardust
どうだっていい言を 嘘って吐いて戻れない
Spitting out pointless words as lies, I can't go back
時効なんてやってこない 奪ったように奪われて
The statute of limitations never comes, stolen from as I stole
今日だって叶わない 思ったように騙せない
It won't come true today either, I can't deceive as I thought
腐っている僕には 腐ったものしか分からない
Rotten as I am, I only understand rotten things
「おいでここまで」
"Come this far"
「捨てい」
"Stay"
隠してしまったんだ
I've hidden it away
メーデー 僕と判っても もう抱き締めなくて良いんだよ
Mayday, even if you know it's me, you don't have to hug me anymore
ヘイ メーデー 僕が解ったら もう一度笑ってくれるかな
Hey Mayday, if you understand me, will you smile for me once more?
「誠」 幻だって知るんだよ
"Truth" is just an illusion, I know
「誠」 嘘憑きだって知るんだよ ねぇ
"Truth" is just a lie, I know, hey
どうだっていいはずが 今日だって yes を恋い出す
It should be pointless, but today I still crave a "yes"
後悔の脆弱は 騙したほうが正義なの
In the fragility of regret, is the deceiver the righteous one?
卑怯だって構わない 祈っておいてそれはない
I don't care if it's cowardly, don't say that after praying
飾っていた饒舌が 墓穴を掘って焼ける様
The flowery eloquence digs its own grave and burns away
追い目 どこまで
Debt, how far?
グレイ
Gray
被害者面したって
Even if I play the victim
メーデー 僕を叱ってよ 正直者でありたいなら
Mayday, scold me, if you want to be an honest person
ヘイ メーデー 僕を裁いてよ 最後まで甘えてしまうのは
Hey Mayday, judge me, for depending on you until the end
「誠」 亡霊だって知るんだよ
"Truth" is just a ghost, I know
「誠」 空白だって知るんだよ ねぇ
"Truth" is just a blank space, I know, hey
足りないものを望んだら 僕じゃない僕であったよ
When I wished for what I lacked, I became a me that wasn't me
それでも前に進んだの クラクラしちゃう夜も
Even so, I moved forward, through the dizzying nights
足りない僕を愛してよ エゴママが僕を育てたの
Love the incomplete me, my selfish ego raised me
きみには僕が見えるかな 孤濁な...
I wonder if you can see me, in this lonely...
ピエロだ
I'm a clown.
メーデー 僕とわかっても もう抱きしめなくていいんだよ
Mayday, even if you realize it's me, you don't have to hold me anymore.
メーデー 僕がわかったら もう一度笑ってくれるかな
Mayday, if you understand me, will you smile for me once more?
メーデー 僕を叱ってよ 正直者が夢見たいなら
Mayday, scold me, if the honest person wants to dream.
メーデー 僕を裁いてよ 最後まで甘えてしまうのは
Mayday, judge me, for relying on you until the very end.
メーデー 僕を暴いてよ もう直き終わるこの世界から
Mayday, expose me, from this world that is about to end.
メーデー 僕と踊ってよ 最初からいないとわかってた
Mayday, dance with me, I knew from the start I wasn't there.
幻だって知るんだよ
I know it's just an illusion.
嘘つきだって知るんだよ
I know I'm a liar.
亡霊だって知るんだよ
I know I'm a ghost.
空白だって知るんだよ
I know it's just a void.
どうだっていい言を 嘘って吐いて戻れない
Spitting out lies about trivial things, I can't go back.
時効なんてやってこない 奪ったように奪われて
Statute of limitations will never come, being taken just as I took.
至上主義アドトラック
Shijou Shugi Ad Truck
目合わせ 始まるシナプス 定め
Eye contact, the synapses begin to fire, fate.
麗しき 途端の意思疎通
Beautiful, immediate mutual understanding.
無意味な 賞賛 満足げ 卑近の見本市
Meaningless praise, looking satisfied, a trade fair of the mundane.
うつろに 貌 信心 丁重
Hollowly, face, faith, courtesy.
凸凹 すりかざした 詭弁
Unevenness, brandishing sophistry.
着せ替えた 顔持つ 疲れ果て
Exhausted, having a face that was changed.
張り替えられた 皮が ひび割れてゆく
The replaced skin begins to crack.
完膚なきまでに 潰れた この場面 捨てては
Discarding this place that was completely crushed.
刻まれた 皺 すり減らす 底へ
To the bottom where the carved wrinkles are worn down.
あぁ 応えを
Ah, give me an answer.
至上主義アドトラックで
On the supremacy ad truck,
四六時中 駆け回る
running around 24/7.
所詮 使い捨ての 消耗品だと
After all, just a disposable consumable.
もっと いい気になんなよ
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
パッと 打ち上げてやれ 夜を飲み込む 星の花
Fire it off with a bang, the flower of stars that swallows the night.
また 重ねられていく 祈り
Prayers are piled up again,
混ぜ放つ
mixed and released.
最高美の 本拠 今日も 騒々
The base of supreme beauty, today is noisy again.
鋭利な 景気 板挟み
Caught between sharp business conditions.
息詰まる 姿で 天上
A suffocating figure, the heavens,
窮地の袋小路
a dead end in a predicament.
雨にも 負けず 風にも負けず
Unyielding to rain, unyielding to wind.
錆びついている 消息 不条理に
The news is rusted, irrationally.
軋みを 増した 歯車は 北風のせいと
The creaking gears are blamed on the north wind,
見限られてゆく
and are abandoned.
変わり映えのない 凡夫の 落涙 晴らしては
Clearing away the tears of an unremarkable commoner.
弾かれた 枠 すり抜ける 古い
Slipping through the excluded frame, old.
あぁ 応えは
Ah, the answer is...
至上主義アドトラックで
On the supremacy ad truck,
唯一無二を 吊り下げる
hanging the one and only.
所詮 及ばずの 代用品だと
After all, just an inadequate substitute.
おい 今に 見とけよ
Hey, just you watch.
パッと 仕掛けて やれば 夜に 靡かれる 星の花
If I set it off with a bang, the flower of stars swayed by the night.
また ひとつ 指で 押し開けていく
Opening up another one with my finger,
祈り 横へ すべらせる
sliding the prayer sideways.
閉塞したままの 感情 線 逃れる手は
The hand to escape the emotional line that remains blocked.
鳴らされた 理想 押し退ける 現実
Reality pushing aside the sounded ideal.
あぁ 応えを
Ah, give me an answer.
至上主義アドトラックで
On the supremacy ad truck,
四六時中 駆け回る
running around 24/7.
所詮 使い捨ての 消耗品だと
After all, just a disposable consumable.
もっと いい気になんなよ
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
パッと 打ち上げてやれ 夜を飲み込む 星の花
Fire it off with a bang, the flower of stars that swallows the night.
所詮 及ばずの 代用品だと
After all, just an inadequate substitute.
おい 今に 見とけよ
Hey, just you watch.
パッと 仕掛けて やれば 夜に たゆとう 星の花
If I set it off with a bang, the flower of stars drifting in the night.
また 空に 散りばめられていく 祈り もっと
Prayers being scattered in the sky once more, even more.
...舞い上がる
...dancing up
Na na na na na...
深愛
Deep Love
作詞：水樹奈々　作曲：上松範康 (Elements Garden)
Lyrics: Nana Mizuki / Composition: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
雪が舞い散る夜空
The snow dances in the night sky
二人寄り添い見上げた
Two people snuggling and looking up
繋がる手と手の温もりは
The warmth of our linked hands
とても優しかった
Was very gentle
淡いオールドブルーの雲間に 消えてゆくでしょう
It will probably disappear into the faint old blue clouds
永遠へと続くはずの あの約束
That promise that was supposed to last forever
あなたの側にいるだけで ただそれだけで良かった
Just being by your side, that alone was enough
いつの間にか膨らむ 今以上の夢に気づかずに
Without noticing the dream growing larger than now
どんな時もどこにいる時でも 強く強く抱きしめていて
No matter when, no matter where you are, hold me tight, tight
情熱が日常に染まるとしても
Even if passion becomes part of everyday life
あなたへのこの想いはすべて 終わりなどないと信じている
I believe all these feelings for you will never end
あなただけずっと見つめてるの
I'm only looking at you forever
交わす言葉と時間 姿を変えてゆくでしょう
The words and time we share will probably change shape
白い頬に溶けたそれは 月の涙
That which melted on my white cheeks were the tears of the moon
行かないで、もう少しだけ 何度も言いかけては
"Don't go, just a little bit more," I started to say it many times
「また会えるよね、きっと」 何度も自分に問いかける
"We'll meet again, right? Surely," I ask myself many times
突然走り出した 行き先の違う二人、もう止まらない
Suddenly, we started running in different directions, we can't stop anymore
沈黙が想像を越え 引き裂いて
Silence exceeds imagination and tears us apart
一つだけ許される願いがあるなら 「ごめんね」と伝えたいよ
If there's only one wish that's allowed, I want to say "I'm sorry"
いくら思っていても届かない 声にしなければ動き出さなきゃ
No matter how much I think, it won't reach; I must put it into words, I must start moving
隠しても瞳の奥の二人、 このまま忘れられてしまうの?
Even if we hide, will the two of us in the back of our eyes be forgotten like this?
だから、ねぇ、早く 今ここに来て
So, hey, hurry, come here now
あなたの側にいるだけで ただそれだけで良かった
Just being by your side, that alone was enough
今度巡り会えたら もっともっと笑い合えるかな
If we can meet again, I wonder if we can laugh together more and more
どんな時もどこにいる時でも 強く強く抱きしめていて
No matter when, no matter where you are, hold me tight, tight
情熱より熱い熱で溶かして
Melt me with a heat hotter than passion
あなたへのこの想いはすべて 終わりなどないと信じている
I believe all these feelings for you will never end
はいということで、４曲連続でお送りしました。わー！
Yes, and so, we've presented 4 songs in a row. Yay!
今回は、えっと、ちょっとね、深愛リベンジできたんじゃないかと思うんですけど。
This time, well, I think I was able to have a bit of a "Deep Love" revenge.
どう...どうですか？深愛、あの、２年前のこと覚えてます？みんな、あのちょっと、ケーキがやばかった時の...
How... how was it? "Deep Love", do you guys remember what happened 2 years ago? When the cake was a bit of a disaster...
ああ、ああ、できた、できてた？
Ah, ah, I did it? Was it okay?
あ、よかった、よかった。できてたみたいです。よかった、よかった。いぇーい！
Oh, good, good. It seems I did it. Good, good. Yay!
というわけで、えっと、今回、ゲストにフレア、わため、そしてかなたん、あずちゃん、ルイ姉に来てもらいました。ありがとう！
So, this time, I had Flare, Watame, Kanatan, AZKi-chan, and Lui-nee come as guests. Thank you!
ちょっとね、うちが歌ってみたいなっていうふうに思ったメンバーに、えーと、オファーをかけさせてもらって...
I reached out to members I really wanted to sing with...
そのメンバーに合うんじゃないかなっていう曲を独断と偏見で選ばせてもらいました。一緒に歌えてめちゃくちゃ楽しかったです。ありがとうございました。
...and I took the liberty of choosing songs that I thought would suit them perfectly. It was so much fun singing together. Thank you so much.
というわけで、えー、すごいね、最高のステージを作れたなと思うんですけど。
And so, well, I think we've created an amazing stage.
ここからもね、まだまだあるのでね、皆さん楽しみにしていていただければと思います。
But there's still more to come, so I hope you're all looking forward to it.
楽しみだな。うちも楽しみなんだよね。
I'm excited. I'm excited too.
で、なんと次が新ステージがあるみたいな噂なんですけれども。
And, word has it that there's a new stage coming up next.
おや、おや、おや。そろそろ準備もできたみたいなので。
Oh, oh, oh. It looks like the preparations are just about done.
うちも行ってきます！みんなも一緒に会場に移動しよう！
I'm off then! Let's all move to the venue together!
おっとっと、ちょっと、ちょっと。
Whoa, wait, wait.
おい、トラックの上に人乗せたまま動いちゃダメだよ！
Hey, you can't move the truck while there's someone on top!
愛も僕も生まれる前、夜もずっと昔から続くように
Just like the night has continued since long before love or I were born
どういつも傷つけ合って、また愛し合うのさ
Why do we always hurt each other, and then love each other again?
結構なしごとの途中、またちょっとつまずいてたとしても
Even if I'm stumbling a bit in the middle of some great work
そう僕も他人事なんかじゃない、分かってるのさ
Yeah, it's not like it's someone else's problem, I know that
イェイ、明けない夜はないと、夜明け前がただ暗いと
Yeah, they say there's no night that doesn't end, and that it's just darkest before the dawn
この先に待つ明日が、そんなに輝くもんかな
I wonder if the tomorrow waiting ahead will really shine that brightly
今 I LOVE YOU で始まる僕らを、もっと照らしてくれよ
Now, shine more light on us, starting with "I LOVE YOU"
変わらないアイの形を、まだ信じてみたいのさ
I still want to believe in an unchanging form of love
ほら I MISS YOU であきらめムードでも、ワンステップ飛ばしてゆけよ
Look, even if it's an "I MISS YOU" giving-up mood, let's skip a step and go
時代遅れの愛が、たまに待ち受けるけど 愛を歌う
Old-fashioned love sometimes waits for us, but I'll sing of love
あの子が届かなかったことで、いつも悩んだりしているのは
The reason why I'm always worried about what that girl couldn't reach
見ちゃえばあだ名といつから、決まってたのさ
Was because it was decided once I saw it and gave it a nickname
イェイ、なんとなく恋に落ちて、いつの間にか本気だって
Yeah, somehow falling in love, and before I knew it, I was serious
張り裂けそうな胸の奥を、打ち明けなくちゃな
I have to reveal the depth of my heart that feels like it's bursting
今 I LOVE YOU で始まる僕らを、もっと満たしてくれよ
Now, fill us up more, starting with "I LOVE YOU"
イメージ通りにはいかない、としても信じてみたいのさ
Even if things don't go as imagined, I want to try believing
ほら I MISS YOU で賞味期限がある、ほら急かしてくれよ
Look, with an "I MISS YOU" that has an expiration date, look, hurry me up
時代遅れの未来が、待ち受けるけど 愛を歌う
An old-fashioned future awaits us, but I'll sing of love
アドが夜明けまで 君の声が聞きたい
I want to hear your voice until the dawn
あいつの代わり映えしたくてさ
I wanted to make a change instead of him
あぁ僕ら同じことで悩んだり、悲しんだり、笑ったりしてんのにな
Ah, even though we're worrying, being sad, and laughing about the same things
分かり合うのはそう簡単じゃない、ただこんなにも君とリンクしてる
Understanding each other isn't that easy, but I'm linking with you so much
重なってゆく
We're overlapping
今...
Now...
I love youで始まる僕らを
For us, starting with "I love you",
もっと照らしてくれよ
please shine your light on us more.
変わらない愛や
Unaltering love,
希望の類いもまだ
and things like hope—
信じてみたいのさ
I still want to believe in them.
ほら I miss youで
See, with "I miss you",
諦めムードを
this mood of giving up,
でも ぶっ飛ばして行けよ
just blow it all away.
時代柄暗い
In these times,
話題が持ち切りだけど
dark topics are all we hear about, but
愛を歌う
I'll sing of love.
Wow Oh Yeah Yeah
さあ僕が生まれる前より
Now, even before I was born,
ずっと昔から続くように
may it continue as it has since long ago.
そう いつも気付き合って
Yes, always noticing each other,
また 愛し合うのさ
we'll love each other once again.
ストロボナイツ
Strobe Nights
作詞:yae 作曲:kz
Lyrics: yae / Composition: kz
キラリと
Sparkling,
流れてる
it's flowing.
見つけてほしいから
Because I want you to find me,
ここにいるの
I'm right here.
誰かが
Someone
手を伸ばす合図で
gives a signal by reaching out,
そっと
softly,
回る星 蒼く
the revolving stars glow blue,
光って
shining.
初めての冬が来たよ
My first winter has arrived.
誰もいない公園で
In this empty park,
星がぶつかる音に胸が鳴る
the sound of stars colliding makes my heart throb.
ブランコから見上げた空
The sky I looked up at from the swing—
名前はわからないけれど
I don't know its name, but
近づきたいよ 希望になって
I want to get closer and become your hope.
キラリと 走る光
A flash of running light,
みんなが指差して笑ってた
everyone was pointing and laughing at it.
君が私を呼んでる
You're calling out to me.
もっと繋ぐ力にして
Make it a power that connects us more,
届いて
and reach out.
みんな！ ミオの森のステージ作ってもらったよ！
Everyone! They built this "Mio's Forest" stage for me!
ライブはまだまだ、盛り上がっていこう！
The live show is far from over, let's keep the hype going!
Yeah!
綿雲が消えていくの
The cirrus clouds are fading away,
風が運んでいた
carried by the wind.
夜の闇に私の姿写す
My silhouette is reflected in the darkness of the night.
最近は街明かりで
Lately, with all the city lights,
星を忘れてしまう人
people have started to forget the stars.
これがもう最後だから
Since this is the very last time,
見ていてね
please watch me.
キラリと 流れてる
Sparkling, it's flowing.
見つけてほしいから ここにいるの
Because I want you to find me, I'm right here.
誰かが 手を伸ばす合図で
Someone gives a signal by reaching out,
そっと
softly,
回る星 蒼く
the revolving stars glow blue,
光って
shining.
きらきら 光る
Twinkling and shining,
星の欠片
fragments of stars.
見つけてくれたら
If you find them,
ここにいるの
I'm right here.
君が
As you
手を伸ばす合図で
give a signal by reaching out,
そっと
softly,
回る星 蒼く
the revolving stars glow blue,
光って
shining.
手を伸ばす合図で
With the signal to reach out my hand
そっと回る星空に
To the gently spinning starry sky
光って
Shine
きらりと走る星は
The stars that run with a twinkle
思い出すの遊んでいたあの空
I remember the sky where we used to play
はじけて消えてく光の軌跡
The trails of light that burst and fade
また会おうね この空で
Let's meet again in this sky
きっと
Surely
鬼灯日和
Hozuki Biyori
沈む赤灯火
The red light sinking
染まる坂道
The colored slope
伝う雫に
In the trickling droplets
嬉しさ滲む
Joy seeps through
夜の帳の
The veil of night
近づく音に
To the approaching sound
はしゃいだ君の声一つ
The single sound of your merry voice
空に響いていく
Echoes into the sky
稲荷の前で待ち合わせ
Meeting in front of the Inari shrine
連なる鳥居くぐり抜け
Passing through the row of torii gates
鬼灯の淡い影
The faint shadows of the winter cherries
胸をすり抜けていく
Slipping through the heart
踊ろうわよ
Let's dance
廻れ廻れ手を叩いてほら
Turn and turn, clap your hands, look
見よう見まねで輪になって
Imitate what you see and form a circle
ぎこちない振り付けに潜む
Hidden in the awkward choreography
想いはひらひら
Thoughts are fluttering
踊れ踊れ天に仰いで
Dance, dance, looking up to the heavens
上気した頬牡丹色
Flushed cheeks colored like peonies
鳴り響く太鼓の音に
To the echoing sound of the drums
赤い果実弾けた
The red fruit burst open
君に気付けたかな
I wonder if I noticed you
響くざわめき
The echoing commotion
燃ゆる篝火
The burning bonfire
揺らぐ気持ちに
In the wavering feelings
思いなせよ
Just imagine it
祭り囃子
Festival music
遠のく音に
To the fading sound
天狼星の雲隠れ胸を突付いた
Sirius hiding behind the clouds pierced my heart
今宵空には朧月
Tonight, there's a hazy moon in the sky
霞んだ処誤魔化した
I glossed over the hazy parts
佇まい揺らゆらいて
My presence is swaying
胸をすり抜けたら
Once it slips through the heart
目を閉じて
Close your eyes
眠れ眠れ意識を飛ばし
Sleep, sleep, letting your consciousness fly
一夜一夜募る嘘
Lies that pile up night after night
月明かり照らす花びら
Petals illuminated by the moonlight
今はハラハラ
Now they're falling
泣いて泣いて流る雫
Cry and cry, flowing droplets
夜目に見えぬ五月雨
Early summer rain invisible in the night
重なった狐火より
More than the overlapping foxfires
袖の標隠した
I hid the sign on my sleeve
君に気付かぬように
So that you won't notice
鬼灯日和
Onibi Hiyori
#大神ミオ4周年記念
#OokamiMio4thAnniversary
天つ風 雲の通い路
Heavenly wind, the path through the clouds,
閉ざし見ゆる 夢のまにまに
Is closed to my sight, within the drifting dreams.
幾千世 想い焦がれた
For thousands of years, I've longed for this.
このひとときが 絶えませぬように
May this moment never end.
お綴り 願う
I pray for the weaving of our story.
止まれ 止まれ 時間よ止まれ
Stop, stop, oh time, please stop.
夢の心地を ご賞味あれ
Please behold this dreamlike feeling.
狐火の 狼煙にのって
Riding on the signal fire of the foxfire.
さぁ心 ゆらゆら
Now, my heart sways and sways.
踊れ 踊れ 手を取り合わせ
Dance, dance, joining hands.
軽快な歩調を 水鏡
A light step reflected in the water's surface.
幸せの 百鬼夜行
The happy parade of a hundred demons.
連なる 想い出たち
Successive memories.
今宵 君に幸あれ
May luck be with you tonight.
スパークル
Sparkle
歌：大神ミオ / 作詞・作曲：野田洋次郎
Vocals: Ookami Mio / Lyrics, Music: Yojiro Noda
Movie / 近所のにーちゃん
Movie / Kinjo no Ni-chan
まだこの世界は
It seems this world still...
僕を飼いならしてたいみたいだ
...wants to keep me tamed.
望み通りだろう
Just as you wish,
美しくもがくよ
I'll struggle beautifully.
互いの砂時計
Let's kiss while watching...
眺めながらキスをしようよ
...each other's hourglasses.
「さよなら」から一番
Let's meet at the place...
遠い場所で待ち合わせよう
...farthest away from "goodbye".
ついに時はきた
The time has finally come;
昨日までは序章の序章で
until yesterday, it was just the prologue of a prologue.
飛ばし読みでいいから
You can skim through it;
ここからが僕だよ
from here on, it's me.
経験と知識と
With experience, knowledge,
カビの生えかかった勇気を持って
and a moldy courage,
いまだかつてないスピードで
at a speed never seen before,
君のもとへダイブを
I'll dive toward you.
まどろみの中で 生ぬるいコーラに
In my slumber, over a lukewarm cola,
ここでないどこかを夢みたよ
I dreamed of somewhere that isn't here.
教室の窓の外に
Outside the classroom window,
電車に揺られ運ばれる朝に
in the morning being carried by the swaying train.
運命だとか未来だとか
Words like "destiny" or "future",
って言葉がどれだけ手を
no matter how much they reach out,
伸ばそうと届かない
we fall in love in a place...
場所で僕ら恋をする
...where they can't reach.
時計の針も二人を
The hands of the clock also move forward,
横目に見ながら進む
looking at us both out of the corner of their eye.
こんな世界を二人で 一生
Let's live through this world together...
いや、何章でも
for a lifetime, no, for as many chapters as it takes.
生き抜いていこう
Let's survive.
「初めまして」なんてさ
Pushing "nice to meet you"...
遥か彼方へと追いやって
...far, far away,
千年周期を
let's breathe a thousand-year cycle...
一日で息しよう
...in a single day.
辞書にある言葉で
I hated a world made up...
出来上がった世界を憎んだ
...of words found in a dictionary.
8月の、ある朝
On a certain morning in August
君は僕の前で
You were before me
はにかんでは澄ましてみせた
Bashfully trying to look composed
この世界の教科書
Like the textbook of this world
のような笑顔で
With a smile like that
嘘みたいな日々を 規格外の意味を
Making sense of these surreal, extraordinary days
悲劇だっていいから望んだよ
Even if it's a tragedy, it's what I wanted
そしたらドアの外に
And then, outside the door
君が全部抱えて立ってたよ
There you were, carrying everything with you
運命だとか未来とかって言葉が
In a place where words like "destiny" or "future"
どれだけ手を 伸ばそうと届かない 場所で
can't reach, no matter how much they try to stretch out...
僕ら遊ぼうか
Shall we play?
愛し方さえも 君の匂いがした
Even the way I loved smelled like you
歩き方さえも その笑い声がした
Even the way I walked sounded like your laughter
いつか消えてなくなる
One day it will all disappear
君のすべてを
Everything about you
この目に焼き付けておくことはもう
Burning your everything into my eyes
権利なんかじゃない
is no longer just a right
義務だと思うんだ
I think it's a duty
運命だとか未来とかって言葉が
In a place where words like "destiny" or "future"
どれだけ手を 伸ばそうと届かない 場所で
can't reach, no matter how much they try to stretch out,
僕ら恋をする
we fall in love
時計の針も二人を
As the hands of the clock advance,
横目に進む
watching us from the side
そんな世界を二人で
Let's live through such a world together
一生 いや、何章でも 生き抜いていこう
for a lifetime, no, for as many chapters as it takes
というわけで、スパークルでしたー！
So that was "Sparkle"!
いい曲だよね。
It's such a great song.
初めての歌ってみたということで、とても思い出深い曲です。ありがとうございます。
It was my first ever cover song, so it's a very memorable one for me. Thank you.
というわけで、4曲、一気にお送りさせてもらいました！
And with that, I've performed four songs in a row!
そして新ステージだー！イェーイ！
And look at this new stage! Yay!
かわいい！
It's so cute!
なんかいろいろちょっと触れたいところあるんだけど、
There's so much I want to talk about,
まずは、ちょっとゲストに来てもらったので、ゲストの皆さんをご紹介しましょう。
but first, I have some guests with me, so let me introduce them.
こより、フブキ、そしてあやめに来てもらいました！わー、ありがとう！めっちゃ可愛かった。
Koyori, Fubuki, and Ayame came to join me! Wow, thank you! They were so cute.
えっとね、こよりにはね、「よもすがら君想ふ」を歌ってもらおうと思、歌ってもらったんですけど、
So, I had Koyori sing "Yomosugara Kimi Omou,"
すごいね、合いそうだなって思って選曲したら、
and when I picked it because I thought it would really suit her,
なんかこよりも「歌いたかったんです」って言ってくれて、すっごく嬉しかったです。めっちゃ可愛かった。
Koyori told me, "I've always wanted to sing this," which made me so happy. She was so cute.
そしてね、うちが大好きなグループの大好きな曲、 「鬼灯日和」を歌わせてもらいました。
And then, we sang a favorite song from a group I love, "Hoozuki Biyori."
あやめとフブキも相変わらずとっても可愛かったです。普遍の可愛さ。
Ayame and Fubuki were as cute as ever. An unchanging cuteness.
そして！この新ステージ！
And! This new stage!
「森の中のパーティーライブ」っていうコンセプトで作ってもらったんですけど、
It was built with the concept of a "party live in the forest,"
おお、なんか、足元になんかうちからすごいよく見えるんだけどさ、
oh, I can see something at my feet really clearly from up here,
っ、すごい、いっぱいいる！
W-wow, there's so many!
ミオファのみんながすごいいっぱいいるんだよ。
There are so many Mio-fa here.
しかもなんか綺麗に整列しててｗ
And they're all lined up so neatly (laughs).
かわいい！ちゃんとオオカミver.とデコver.がいる。
So cute! There's both the wolf version and the decorated version.
しかも...
And...
なんか手がすごい短くてサイリウムがめちゃくちゃ振りにくそうなんだけれどもね
Your hands are so short, it looks like it's really hard to wave those penlights...
みんな頑張ってね、あの、サイリウムではなく自分が揺れることでね、応援してくれてますね
Everyone is doing their best, cheering me on by swaying themselves instead of the penlights.
かわいい！
So cute!
けど後ろから見るとなんか灰色の草が揺れてるみたいだなぁ
But from the back, it looks like grey grass is swaying...
すごいかわいい。ちょっと後でね、
Very cute. A bit later,
モフったりとかしたいんですけれども、君たち立体化したんだねー
I want to fluff you all, you've all become 3D!
はい、というわけでちょっと新しいものが多すぎて、なんか全然追いつかないんですけれども
Yes, well, there are so many new things that I can't keep up with them all.
ま、いっぱい用意してくれた運営さん本当にありがとうございました。ありがとうございました。
Anyway, thank you so much to the staff for preparing all of this. Thank you.
さて、えー、まだまだちょっとライブは続くんですけれども、次ちょっとそろそろ行こうかなーと思います
Now then, the live is still going on, and I think it's about time to move on to the next one.
なんかみんな気づいてる？
Is everyone noticing?
あの、ついこの間うちオリジナル曲出したよね。
You know, I just released an original song the other day.
それまだ聞いてないなって思うよね。
I'm thinking I haven't heard that yet.
うんうん。ちょっと準備してくるから。あははは。
Yeah, yeah. I'm going to go get ready. Hahaha.
じゃあちょっと準備してきますね。みんな楽しみにしてて、
Well then, I'll go get ready. Everyone look forward to it,
最後まで絶対見てね！いってきます！
and be sure to watch until the very end! Here I go!
ネオンライトは眩く
Neon lights are dazzling
街灯明滅 通り過ぎ
Passing by the blinking streetlights
窓の向こう 夜の風に
Beyond the window, in the night wind
空を見た
I looked at the sky
サヨナラは、まだ
作詞・作曲: 河合泰志, 山本恭平 (Arte Refact)
編曲: 河合泰志, 山本恭平, 脇眞富 (Arte Refact)
"Goodbye is not yet"
Lyrics & Composition: Taishi Kawai, Kyohei Yamamoto (Arte Refact)
Arrangement: Taishi Kawai, Kyohei Yamamoto, Masatomi Waki (Arte Refact)
忙しない足取り
Hectic footsteps
まばらなノイズ
Sparse noise
私だけが 取り残されたようで
As if I'm the only one left behind
ゆめうつつ
In a half-awake dream
また光に揺られる
Swayed by the light again
心の中で私を消して
Erasing myself within my heart
追いかけた過去 背中合わせの
The past I chased, back-to-back
希望 密度 押しつぶされぬよう
So that hope and density won't crush me
だから君と ここにいる時間は
That's why the time I spend here with you
せめて
At least
言葉にできず 見つめ合うだけ
Just staring at each other, unable to put it into words
思考回路 ぼやけたままで さあ
With my thought process remaining blurred, now
光を掴むまで
Until I grasp the light
サヨナラは、まだ
Goodbye is not yet
暗いカーテン 向こうの
Beyond the dark curtains
偏光反射 籠の鳥
Polarized reflections, a bird in a cage
閉じた心 隠したくて
Wanting to hide my closed heart
ふと一人
Suddenly alone
また光に溺れる
Drowning in the light again
呼吸する暇もなくて 沈む
Sinking without even a moment to breathe
時の狭間で 隣り合わせの
Side by side in the gap of time
理想 現実 押しつぶされぬよう
So that ideals and reality won't crush me
だから私 繋がっていたいの
That's why I want to be connected
君と
With you
見つめ合うたび 微笑み合って
Smiling at each other every time our eyes meet
だけど君は ぼやけたままでさ
But you remain blurred
巡り すれ違って
Coming across each other, passing by each other
惹かれ合う また
Attracted to each other once again
(Endless Night, Endless Light)
(Inner the Cage, Outside the Cage)
逃げ出してみたい
I want to try running away
(This story will end, though)
心 離れずに溺れ...
Drowning without letting go of my heart...
未来に魅入られる
Enchanted by the future
夢の中なら私と きっと
In a dream, with me, surely
追いかけた過去 背中合わせの
The past I chased, back-to-back
希望 密度 押しつぶされぬよう
So that hope and density won't crush me
だから君と ここにいる時間は
That's why the time I spend here with you
せめて
At least
言葉にできず 見つめ合うだけ
Just staring at each other, unable to put it into words
思考回路 ぼやけたままで さあ
With my thought process remaining blurred, now
光を掴むまで
Until I grasp the light
サヨナラは、まだ
Goodbye is not yet
聴こえますか
Can you hear me?
ハロー　ハロー　聴こえますか
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
そっちは何年？
What year is it over there?
正しく分かり合う手段は
The means to truly understand each other
一つじゃないさ
Aren't just one
漂う時間は何処へ行くのか
Where does the drifting time go?
さよならは　いつ誰が決めるの
When and who decides on "goodbye"?
その手に触れようと願ってる
I wish to touch those hands
本当さ
It's true
永遠の夜光　君に歌う
Singing the eternal night-light to you
世界中が　君にいじわるでも
Even if the whole world is mean to you
思い出して　覚えていて
Recall, and remember
瞼の裏　ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind those eyelids, we can always meet again
穏やかに　健やかに
Gently, healthily
枯れるブーケ
A withering bouquet
君だって　私だって
You and even I
消えるのは　言葉だけ
Only the words will disappear
ふんわり　君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll gently hold you close
泣かないで
Don't cry
延々と続く今日は　雪原のようで
Today continues on like a snowy field
当然の幸せまでも　眩ませるんだ
Even blinding us to natural happiness
忘れないで
Don't forget
何処へだって繋がる　回線
The circuit that connects anywhere
寂しい宇宙と　オレンジの公園
The lonely universe and the orange park
慕わしい心の限りを
With all my yearning heart
歌おう
Let's sing
永遠の夜光　届くよね
The eternal night-light will reach you, right?
幻想よりも　優しいかたちのまま
In a form gentler than any illusion
濡れそぼる　その頬を
Those damp cheeks
こっそり撫でて　乾かしてあげるからね
I'll secretly stroke and dry them for you
何度だって
Time and time again
永遠の夜光　虚空に歌う
Singing the eternal night-light to the void
会いたいよ　消えたしなんてないよ
I want to see you, I don't want to disappear
思い出して　覚えていて
Recall, and remember
今　ここで笑い合ったことを
That we laughed together here and now
永遠の夜光　君に歌う
Singing the eternal night-light to you
世界中が　君にいじわるでも
Even if the whole world is mean to you
思い出して　覚えていて
Recall, and remember
瞼の裏　ずっとまた会えるからね
Behind those eyelids, we can always meet again
さよならは　さよならは
Goodbye, goodbye
ねぇ誰が　決めるもの
Hey, who's the one that decides?
消えるのは　言葉だけ
Only the words will disappear
ふんわり　君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll gently hold you close
泣かないで
Don't cry
はい、えーみんな、びっくりした？
Hi, uh, everyone, were you surprised?
新曲2曲続けてお送りしました。
I've performed two new songs back-to-back.
1曲目は「サヨナラは、まだ」、そして2曲目は「夜光通信」、いかがでしたでしょうか。
The first was "Sayonara wa, Mada," then "Yakou Tsuushin." How did you like them?
どちらもめっちゃカッコよくて、うちはお気に入りです。
Both are super cool, and I really love them.
あのね「夜光通信」、2曲目の「夜光通信」なんですけど、
About "Yakou Tsuushin," the second one,
この後MVを投稿するのでぜひ一緒に見て欲しいです。
I'll be posting its MV after this, so I'd love for us to watch it together.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
というわけでね、何か...圧を感じる...あ、なんかめちゃくちゃデカくない？
And so... I feel some... pressure... Oh, aren't they incredibly big?
何でこんなデカくなったんだ？ まぁこの2匹はちょっとあの、後でメンバーシップ限定の放送をこの後やる予定なので、
Why did they get so big? Well, I'm planning to do a members-only stream after this,
メンバーシップ限定の放送の時にご紹介したいと思います。はい。
So I'll introduce them then. Yes.
というわけで、えーちょっと以上になるんだよね、寂しいんだけどさ、
So, uh, that's about it. It's a bit sad but...
ちょっと、うちみんなにお手紙書いてきたからそれを読んでもいい？
Wait, I wrote a letter to everyone, so can I read it?
ちょっと、ちょっと待っててね。
Wait, just a moment, please.
はい。というわけで、みんなにお手紙書いてきたので、聞いてください。
Alright. So, I've written a letter for everyone, so please listen.
えー、すべてのミオファ、そしてホロライブファンの皆へ。
To all Miofas, and to all Hololive fans.
デビューしてからの4年間、あっという間でした。
The four years since my debut have gone by in a flash.
最初にデビューした時は、とにかくがむしゃらで、色々模索したり、勝手に悩んで病んだりしていました。
When I first debuted, I was just reckless, searching for my way, worrying on my own and feeling down.
この4年間は、本当に語りきれないぐらい楽しいことも嬉しいこともありました。
These past four years, there have been so many fun and happy things I couldn't possibly talk about them all.
でも、泣いたり笑ったりしながらも、ホロライブを応援し続けてくれたみんな、
But, through the tears and the laughter, everyone who continued to support Hololive,
そして、うち、大神ミオを応援し続けてくれたみんながいてくれたから、4周年をこうして迎えることができたんだと心の中の底から思っています。
and everyone who continued to support me, Ookami Mio, I believe from the bottom of my heart that it's thanks to you that I was able to reach this 4th anniversary.
本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much.
これから5年目をみんなと歩むことになりますが、いっぱいっぱい笑って過ごそうね。
From now on, I'll be walking into my 5th year with all of you, so let's spend it laughing a whole lot, okay?
うちのことをみんなが愛してくれるように、うちもみんなのことを愛しています。
Just as you all love me, I love you all too.
5年目もよろしくね。ミオより。
Please look after me in my 5th year too. From Mio.
あ、ちょっと恥ずかしい。はは。
Ah, that's a bit embarrassing. Haha.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや、すごい、みんなにはすごく感謝してるんだ。ありがとう。
No, really, I'm so grateful to everyone. Thank you.
今日はちょっと終わっちゃうの寂しいけど、普通の放送もぜひ見に来てください。
I'm a bit sad it's ending today, but please come watch my regular broadcasts too.
というわけで、ありがとね、みんな。
So, thank you, everyone.
バイバーイ！寂しい。バイバーイ！
Bye-bye! It's lonely. Bye-bye!
はい！グッズ紹介担当の、大神ミオです！パンパカパーン！
Yes! I'm Ookami Mio, in charge of the merch introduction! Pam-pa-ka-paan!
大神ミオ 活動4周年記念 12月7日 販売開始
Ookami Mio 4th Anniversary Celebration. Sales start December 7th.
4周年記念グッズが発売されます！わー！
4th anniversary merch is now on sale! Yay!
気になる内容のご紹介！
Let's introduce the items you're curious about!
まずは、泉パパ描き下ろし、アクリルジオラマスタンド！
First, the acrylic diorama stand, newly illustrated by Izumi-papa!
アクリルジオラマスタンド イラスト：泉彩
Acrylic Diorama Stand. Illustration: Izumi Sai.
なんと昨日お披露目の新衣装グッズです！
It's merch featuring the new outfit unveiled yesterday!
ちょっとポーズがセクシーなんだけど、ミオファがとっても可愛い。
The pose is a bit sexy, but the Miofas are so cute.
そしてそして、マグカップ！
And then, a mug!
マグカップ イラスト：森永亜亜
Mug. Illustration: Morinaga Aa.
うちが温かいお茶をよく飲むので、あったら嬉しいなーって思って作りました。
I drink hot tea often, so I made it thinking it'd be nice to have one.
みんなもお揃いのマグでお茶飲もうね。
Let's all drink tea with matching mugs.
そして、なんと待望の！
And then, the long-awaited!
ミオファぬいぐるみ オオカミの姿 / ネコの姿
Miofa Plushie (Wolf form) / (Cat form)
ミオファぬいぐるみかける2！オオカミの姿と、猫の姿、両方同時の発売です！
Miofa plushies times two! Both the wolf form and the cat form are being released at the same time!
めっちゃ可愛い！クオリティ重視で作ってもらいました。
They're so cute! I had them made with a focus on quality.
早くお家に来てほしいな。
I want them to come to your homes soon.
そして、今回特典が、あります！
And, there are purchase bonuses this time!
まずはボイスが二つ！みんなへの感謝の気持ちボイスと、シチュエーションボイスの二つです。
First, two voice packs! An "Expression of Gratitude to Everyone" voice and a "Situation Voice".
フルセット購入特典：直筆サイン入り 複製箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード
Full Set Purchase Bonus: Postcard with handwritten signature and duplicated foil-stamped message.
ボイス録音はいつもちょっと恥ずかしいけど、ありがとうの気持ち聞いてほしいな。
Recording voices is always a bit embarrassing, but I want you to hear my feelings of gratitude.
さらに、今年も頑張ります！大神ミオ直筆サイン入り、複製箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード！
Furthermore, I'll be working hard again this year! A postcard with Ookami Mio's handwritten signature and a duplicated foil-stamped message!
こちら数量限定なしで、フルセット購入の方全員に、サインを書かせていただきます。
There's no limited quantity for this; I'll be signing for everyone who buys the full set.
一枚一枚思いを込めて書くよ。
I'll write each one with all my heart.
以上、グッズ紹介でした！
That concludes the merch introduction!
このあと、メンバーシップ限定の放送もあるので、お楽しみに！
There's a membership-exclusive broadcast coming up after this, so look forward to it!
4周年記念ライブ、すっごく楽しかった！
The 4th anniversary live was so much fun!
5年目も一緒に、楽しい思い出いっぱい作ろうね。
Let's make lots of fun memories together in the 5th year too.
ありがとう！おつみおーん！
Thank you! Otsu-Mioon!